Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
WEB-DL resync by GoldenBeard
www.addic7ed.com
You're not supposed
to be here.
You know better.
It's a beautiful night.
Share it with me.
You can get yourself back in.
You're mad.
- Birdie.
- Don't call me that.
We can skip your exercise.
You fit that in last night.
I was...
trying to talk to you.
I'm not interested
in that talk.
- Anna...
- No.
It won't change anything.
Hey.
You must be Anna.
Who are you?
Oh. sweetie.
did he not tell you
that I was coming?
I'm the lawyer.
So your brother's
already approved these.
He's taken care of everything.
so when the time comes.
you won't have to make
any arrangements.
I just need a signature.
Anna. I'm here to help Conrad
get what he wants.
What he wants is for you
to be taken care of.
My mother had it too.
Not pancreatic. but...
I do know how hard it is.
And acceptance is only a choice
that you can make.
Then I won't choose.
Submitted for your approval.
Today's offering:
meatloaf.
Loaf: confirmed. Meat:
jury's out.
Green beans almondine:
nutty. beanie.
And the pièce de résistance?
Apple cobbler:
sweet. tart.
Uh-huh.
Uh... it's...
it's really good.
This a bad time?
No. she was just leaving.
As soon as I get a signature.
Okay. alright...
I got you.
Okay. Okay. It's okay.
I don't know how I'm gonna
do this without you.
Ah...
I'll be with you.
You don't believe
in that stuff.
I'm not talking
about that stuff.
I'm talking about us.
What we've been through
together.
You're stronger now
because of it.
Hey...
you can't stay locked up
forever.
You have to get out
and be a part of the world.
I want to leave me alone.
That's not the way it works.
It's time to forgive Dad.
- Birdie...
- Stop.
I will never forgive him
for what he did.
Anna...
I have terrible news.
Beef Stroganoff.
But there's a glimmer of hope.
Tater tots!
Maybe it's good.
He's not suffering anymore.
There's gotta be some kind
of relief in that. right?
You've been so strong
this whole time.
Never heard you complain.
Not once.
On this job. trust me.
it's rare.
It's not a relief.
Yeah... sorry.
that came out wrong.
All I mean is...
it's impressive. you know.
You're impressive.
So what's the plan. then?
Are you... gonna keep the place.
or...
What?
Are you gonna keep the place?
Oh. of course.
Where would I go?
No. it's just some people need
to leave in order to move on.
But... this is my home.
Yeah. okay.
Could you leave that easily?
You know.
I shouldn't have asked.
No. Could you?
Well... not everybody feels
so strongly about home.
Not everybody feels
like they have a home.
- Then why haven't you left?
- One guess.
Girlfriend.
No.
I haven't really made the best
decisions in that department.
Whoa.
That's your last reason
for not leaving. right?
Uh. I...
I...
I can't take this.
No. I have more than I know
what to do with. honest.
Take it.
Make your escape.
I'm sorry.
I just can't.
Hello.
You've reached
the Rook residence.
Conrad and Anna
aren't available right now.
If you leave a message.
I will return your call.
Hey. Anna.
This is Charlotte.
I was just thinking about you.
and I wanted to let you know
how proud I am of you for.
you know. facing your fears.
and getting out there and
going to your brother's funeral.
Um. so I guess
I'll see you there.
Okay. bye-bye.
Hey. Anna. This is Charlotte.
I know you've been struggling.
but you can do this.
I'll see you at the funeral.
sweetie. Stay strong.
Anna. are you there?
Anna. please pick up the phone.
Look. the funeral's starting.
If you leave now.
you can still make it.
Please come.
I really hope you...
Hey. go around back.
And don't let anyone see you.
Alright. let's make this quick.
You know what to look for.
What's that?
Find her. Cut the phone line.
Ah!
She's upstairs!
What the hell?
You're not supposed to be here.
Please. stop looking at me.
Please. okay?
Explain it to me.
Why aren't you
at your brother's funeral?
You're Anna. right?
Okay. Anna...
I need you
to be straight with me.
I need to know
where you keep the money.
What are you doing?
Always be prepared.
I'm sorry. prepared for what?
This is fucking crazy. JP.
We should just fucking leave.
goddammit!
Use my name again.
why don't you?!
Go ahead!
There's nothing
on the scanner.
So... looks like
she didn't call anybody.
Did you?
You're an odd bird.
Look at me.
Three men break into your home
and you don't call the police?
I was scared.
I... didn't have time to think.
I have a solution.
Just a quick little love tap
behind the ear.
We are not doing that!
- Hey.
- Then we burn this fucker down.
Fucking Chri...
you gonna stop this shit?
Hey. go make some coffee.
- What?
- Go make some coffee.
Go.
Let the adults talk.
Ah. fuck it.
So?
We're not killing anyone.
Can I leave you alone with her
without making a mess of things?
- Of course.
- I mean it.
- I'm calm as fuck.
- Hey. I mean it.
Scout's honour.
They don't have any coffee.
Forget it.
I've got a plan.
Ah. yeah?
You always got a plan.
You always expect me
to be a part of it.
but I'm not Perry. okay?
I'm not your fucking lapdog!
Look. if you wanna leave.
this is the time to go.
Really?
What about you?
I'm still thinking it through.
Look. I could get the money.
This shit just got
a little complicated.
Yeah. a little.
Look. you're still clean.
little brother.
Let's keep it that way. okay?
Come on. man.
you know I need this money too.
Does that mean
you're with me on this. huh?
All the way.
Let's go find it.
Jesus.
Fucking mess. man.
What was that before?
Just leave me alone. please.
You were gone.
Why didn't you run?
Nowhere to go.
That's not it.
There's something else going on.
Hmm?
What's in there?
Vance. just get started.
I'm gonna get this room.
- Ow.
- You gotta be shitting me.
So you're telling me
you haven't left this house...
in over 10 years?
Yeah.
Okay.
I can just leave this door open.
I can go make myself
a cup of tea.
When I come back...
...you're still sitting there?
That's crazy.
Ah. fuck. that's sad.
This is actually really sad.
Hey. you know what?
I think I can help you.
No. no. no!
- No! No!!
- Huh? C'mere!
Stop. please!
Please. please. please!
- C'mere! C'mere!
- Please stop! Stop!
No. no. no...
See?
It's not so bad.
I got you. I got you. Okay.
What the hell did you do?
She doesn't go outside.
I was just trying to show her.
You gonna be okay?
Perry. go inside.
Hey. I need you to focus.
- Let me back in!
- Hey. hey. we go back inside.
- Perry's gonna kill you.
- I don't care.
Please!!!
Anna. Anna. we looked upstairs
and we didn't find anything.
Look. is there an attic?
Huh? Huh? Safe?
Basement?
Huh? Huh?
Basement? Huh? Basement?
Okay.
Okay. let's get you back inside.
Take her upstairs.
get her cleaned up.
Well. you had your chance
to leave.
Look. don't make me regret
letting you stay.
Fuck.
God-fuckin'...
Put these on.
Hey. you sure you don't
want me to look after her?
- After what you just pulled?
- I'm just saying.
do you really think
Vance is up for this?
He'll be fine.
You gonna tell me
what we're doing down here?
Trust me. man.
we hit the jackpot.
Yeah...
Jackpot.
Uh... what the hell?
Oh. you like sitting around
in your own pee. Got it.
Just change. please.
I... I can't. Ahem.
Ouch.
Sorry.
Fuck!
Come over here man.
Gimme a hand with this.
I'm more curious
what's behind door number two.
Why's that?
No handle.
Uh...
it can be hard...
...to be with someone
who has
such a strong personality.
I can tell...
you're just going along.
I can see it.
Don't you fucking shrink me.
Ow.
Don't think I've dealt
with this my entire life?
Maybe I was the one
who found out about this place.
You ever think about that?
I mean. maybe this whole thing
was my idea?
I don't think you realize
how serious this is.
- No. I do.
- You've seen our faces.
You know our names.
You really think
we're just gonna let you go?
Now put on
the fucking sweatpants!
Stop!
- Please. stop!
- Stop moving. goddammit!
- Stop! Stop...
- Hey! What the hell?!
- Stop it!
- Hey! Get the fuck off her!
- It's not what it looks like!
- What are you doing?
- Honestly...
- Are you okay?
...you gotta listen to me!
She wasn't supposed to be here.
- Listen to me. Danny. please!
- Get back!
Dan...
you guys know each other?
Yes. but that's not...
- No. no.
- Anna. Anna.
- I had nothing to do with this.
- You cannot be here.
- You gotta get out of here. okay?
- Oh. shit!
- Get back.
- You cannot be here. Danny.
Honest. if we knew
she was gonna be here...
- What do you mean. "we"?
- Danny boy.
Leave him alone. dude!
- Don't fucking touch me.
- Where is she?
Huh?
Fuck.
- Hey. hey. hey!
- What?!
Do you know
how this has to end?
We can't let her go.
Just find her.
Come on.
You like to disappear.
don't you?
Come out and play. little girl.
I got a few tricks of my own.
C'mere.
For my next trick.
I would like to invite
my lovely assistant
to the stage.
Anna. would you be so kind
as to join us?
I don't think she's coming.
It's really too bad.
She would've been
of great value to us.
I guess I'll have to do this
on my own.
Hey. Perry!
- Open wide. Dan.
- What the fuck?
Stupid thing didn't talk.
- Ah! Oh!
- I found her!
- You got her?
- Yeah. I got her!
Get the fuck off there! Please.
Don't you understand
I'm the least
of your fucking worries
right now?! Please!
Come on.
He's taking his time.
If he loses her.
we'll find her.
Put out some breadcrumbs.
she'll come.
Come on. man. be serious.
Maybe I am.
You got her?
You hear that?
Stay.
No! No!
Vance!
Vance!!
Vance!!!
Vance!
Wake up!!
Is he dead?
Argh...
Ah. goddamn. Argh...
Ah. Vance.
Hey. Hey! Hey. you. open!
Open it. you fucking bitch!
Open the fucking door!
Anna!
Anna...
Come on!
Hello?
Hey. JP. something weird
is going on here. man.
Come on. we gotta
get the fuck outta here.
Oh. fuck.
You bitch!
You fucking bitch!!
Get down here!
Argh!
Fucking bitch!
Is she making fucking tea?
Hey. nothing in here's
gonna get us up there.
Let's drag
this fucking cabinet in there.
It's bolted to the wall.
- Goddammit!
- Doesn't matter.
She was behind
that fucking door.
and then she was up there.
like that!
The bitch doesn't have wings.
Anna!
Anna. Help me.
Hurry!
Cut me loose.
Robbing me...
during Conrad's funeral?
No. no.
- They did this. not me!
- Then what are you doing here?
I... I wanted
to be there for you.
You...
you went?
You didn't show.
I got worried.
Was it...
was it nice?
It... it was peaceful.
Nobody came?
No. uh. it was me and...
Charlotte and the priest.
He gave a good talk.
It was... it was really nice.
It's okay.
You know. it was...
just me and him.
We only had each other.
Do you know
you've been bringing us food
for almost a year?
I checked the calendar.
Almost to the day.
It feels like longer.
doesn't it?
A-Anna.
Is that how you do it?
You go into people's homes
and...
...steal their things
and then you call your friends
- to go and steal all of it?
- They're not my friends!
Well... Vance is. but...
...not the other two.
You told him about the money?
I... I...
I told him about you.
I told him about your situation.
And. yeah. I told him
you tried to give me money.
It took me off-guard.
I didn't mean...
I... I couldn't stop
thinking about it.
I couldn't stop
thinking about you.
You know.
I almost believe you this time.
Listen to me.
I get if you hate me.
but you have to believe...
I would never hurt you.
What happened to you?
W-w-why don't you leave
the house?
I haven't left the house
since Daddy died.
Whenever I had a problem.
I could always ask Connie.
Hmm...
He always knew
how to handle any situation.
How would he handle this one?
Oh!!
Ow!! Ow!!
If you meant what you said
in there.
then you have to trust me.
I do.
Then you have to jump.
No!
It'll be much safer
if you turn around.
- I'm not... I'm not doing that.
- None of this would've happened
if you would've just taken
the money!
You're not like this.
You have no idea
what I'm like.
Ah!
You don't know me.
Help me!
- What the fuck are you doing?!
- Hey! Shut up!
Fuck. man.
Fuck...
Please help.
Alright. fine.
Fuckin' let me
take a look at it.
Oh... Caref... Ow.
Careful. careful... Ow.
- Oh.
- What. is it bad?
Fuck. it's bad.
Kneecap's dislocated.
Fuck.
Okay...
I'm gonna have to pop it
back into place
before the swelling is too bad
I won't be able to. okay?
- Dan.
- Huh?
It's gonna hurt.
Oh...
JP.
Hey! JP.
Hold his body down.
Hold him down here.
Three. two...
That was kinda fun.
You're alright.
Thank you.
Whatever.
Vance?
Vance!
- He's dead. Shut the fuck up!
- Hey. let it go.
Let it go? We had her
until this shitheel showed up.
I said we should do this
just us.
You didn't want to.
I said take care of that bitch.
You said no.
Now we're stuck
in a fucking basement
with one live piece of shit
and one dead one!
Fuck you!
Get a hold of yourself.
I'm a hold!
I'm a hold of my fucking self!
Just re-evaluate your fucking
priorities. okay. JP?
I'm not the one who's slipping.
JP. JP!
J...
JP?
- Are you okay?
- I...
I... I need to go to a hospital.
I can't... I can't take you
to the hospital.
- No kidding.
- You can't even check
your fucking mail.
you psycho bitch.
- Don't call me that.
- What?
Psycho. or bitch?
We could all stop this.
Let's all stop. okay?
Are you retarded?!
She's not gonna come down here
and fucking save you. Dan!
Can't you get him
under control?
No one fucking controls me.
do you understand?!
Okay...
That's what you get!
I'm cool. I'm okay. JP.
Just breathe.
There's a first-aid kit.
- So go get it.
- No.
- Down there.
- It's locked.
Try again.
Don't go anywhere.
Oh. fuck!
Hey. open this stupid door!
What's in there?
What the fuck?!
Ah...
Perry!
Goddamn!
What the fuck?
Fucking bitch!
Get me outta here!
Hello?
Can you guys hear me?
Yo. Perry. are you there?
- Aren't you gonna do something?
- Oh...
like what?
Get him outta there.
Get him outta there...
Why didn't I think of that?
I should've thought of that.
God. what a fucking idiot.
What an idiot.
Okay. here we go.
We're just gonna
get him outta there.
You just stay seated.
you fucking cripple.
JP. come on out!
Come on. buddy. Huh.
Quit fucking around.
Get me the fuck outta here!
The door seems to be locked.
Do you remember
when that happened?
- What's going on out there?!
- Forget it.
Is that probably
when the door closed?
Did you hear
the locking mechanism?
Hmm...
Yeah.
This'll do.
Come on. big fella.
Goddamn. you fat fuck.
What are you doing?
Putting him in the doorway.
What's it look like?
He's my friend.
He was your friend.
Now. he's a doorstop.
- Hmm?
- Ah...
Fuck.
Fuck you!
Hey... JP.
We're gonna get you out.
Perry's looking for something.
He won't find anything.
He might.
Open it.
you fucking nutty cunt!
Dan... listen to me.
You know
she's not gonna let us go.
Can you blame her?
You were gonna kill her
an hour ago.
Come on.
I was just playing.
Look where it got you.
JP!
She's gonna pay for it.
Fuck this.
JP?
JP. I think
I'm on the other side of you.
Can you hear me?
There's a fucking noose in here.
Hey. Perry!
Can you hear me?
Fuck.
Nice one.
Hello?
Anna?
Is everything okay?
Everything's fine.
Are you okay?
Just...
just a little accident.
Is that Dan's car out front?
Oh!
Dan came to check on me
because I wasn't at the funeral.
So he broke in?
I didn't answer the door.
and he was worried
I was gonna do something bad.
Is there something going on
between you two?
- What? No.
- I knew there was something.
I saw it the other day
when he came over.
Well. I-I've just been so. um.
lonely since Conrad got sick
and I...
Oh. shhh. Honey. it's okay.
Hey. you're going through
a rough time.
You've done nothing wrong.
And if you can't believe that.
you know what you need to do?
No.
Forgive yourself.
Come here.
I'll try.
I'll call you in a few days
just to see how you're doing.
That's nice. thanks.
What is that?
Radiator.
Help!
It's... an old house.
Dan's taking a look at it
for me.
Oh. So sweet.
I'll talk to you soon. okay?
You're in a lot of pain.
aren't you?
Come on. I'll help you.
What'd you do?
Have a seat.
Now lift your legs up.
- Please...
- Now.
You'll understand soon.
What the fuck?
Fuck!
Fuck! God!
Argh! Girly-girl!
You sneaky little fuck!
Argh!
Fuck!
I didn't know you were invited.
Dan.
Perry's dead.
There's a body in the freezer.
Yeah...
You could tell me
there's a unicorn in the attic.
I wouldn't be surprised.
What is this place?
Fucked up. right?
I mean. there's another one
like it upstairs.
Why would you make...
the exact... bedroom?
Are you back there. Anna?
You watching us?
Fu...
We're your zoo animals now?
Huh?
You gonna observe us
in captivity?
Fuck.
Argh!
- Take it easy.
- Fuck!
You can't break it.
It's bulletproof.
You...
There's a shirt
in the dresser.
Put it on.
You know. something tells me
we're not your first guests
here.
You're sitting behind
your little desk. aren't you?
- Huh?
- No.
What's your game. huh?
Who do you watch back there?
What do you do?
Put on the shirt.
What do you do. huh?
Daddy issues?
- Just put on the shirt.
- Or else what?
- Conrad will come.
- Conrad's the dead guy?
You're making it worse.
Anna?
Anna. please open the door.
Not yet.
Not until he puts on the shirt.
Fine! I'll put your shirt on.
I'll play your game.
We're gonna figure this out.
Anna.
You wanna start?
No?!
Fine. I like puzzles.
So you trap some poor fuck
in here...
Conrad sneaks through here.
Yeah?
Fucking airlock?
And he kills them.
Hmm.
Alright.
Simple enough. right?
Just stop.
But if Conrad wants
to kill these guys.
why's he put them in here first?
So you could talk to them.
I... I didn't talk to them.
So it's Conrad. then. huh?
What does he say?
No. no. no. no. wrong question.
What does he want from them?
That's the question.
And what did he do when
he didn't get what he wants?
Hey. you hungry?
Fuck you.
No. no. no. no.
No. no. no. no. no...
Perry said there's a noose
in the other room.
You drugged their food.
Then Conrad came in.
drug them out...
...and he strung them up.
Stop talking.
You know what?
I hate to break it to you.
darling.
but there's no one coming
through that door tonight.
- Conrad's gone.
- Shut up!
You're twisting it around
and you're...
making it sound all wrong!
But... but it's true?
You watched Conrad kill people?
So what?
Supposed to absolve you?
Wh-wh-what is it?
They were killing perverts.
We weren't doing a bad thing.
You have to believe me.
Murder's murder.
No! We were fixing them!
Is that
what you'd tell yourselves?
It's the truth!
They needed our help.
They were sick.
just like Daddy was.
He said he loved me all along.
but... that didn't stop him
from doing what he did to me.
It wasn't so bad after a while.
'cause he would hold me
afterwards and...
Conrad stopped him?
Yeah. he saved me.
He wrapped the sheet
around father's neck
and he pulled it so tight!
When it was all over.
Connie looked at me and I knew.
I knew he would never hurt me.
That he loved me.
That's when you stopped
leaving the house. yeah?
And he built this room
to punish fucking pedophiles
like your dad.
Ah. I saw some twisted
fucking shit. but this...
Pfft. you must be really proud
of yourself.
No. I would've stopped.
but they didn't show me
- they were sorry!
- How would they do that?
Buy you flowers?
Dear Anna.
so sorry to let you down.
- Yours truly. your stand-in dad.
- Stop.
So pleased I got to join you
in your beautiful basement
so we could help you erase
the feeling
of Daddy between your legs.
- Stop...
- Your brother was a sick fuck!
He got his rocks off
killing your dad.
and he wanted to relive
the moment over and over again.
- That's not true.
- Little crazy sister.
little Anna. too scared
to leave. too dumb...
- No!
- Shut the fuck up! Just stop!
Oh. I'm sorry. Dan.
Sorry to mess with your girl.
Dan.
Hmm...?
Come to the mirror.
What do you want?
I want him to pay.
Oh...
Okay. he's dead. Anna.
Okay?
He's been dead for a long time.
No.
Him.
Do it.
Do what now?
I'll let you go.
No.
Please?
I'm not like them.
Just do it!
Now dammit. Dan!
This is how?
This is how they show you
they're sorry?
So much regret.
so much remorse.
that they just...
bang.
They were supposed
to take responsibility
for what they did!
Just like you.
Don't you feel sorry
for what you did?
Big brothers are supposed to
protect their younger siblings.
which is more than you did
for Vance.
- Stop talking about him.
- You know it's your fault!
- Shut your mouth.
- You knew he looked up to you.
You ever wonder if things
would've turned out differently
if only...
I know
what you're trying to do.
It doesn't change the truth.
I could let you go right now.
and there's nowhere you could go
to get away from what you did.
I'm sorry!
Good.
That's good. Now... now show me.
- Oh...
- Show me you're sorry.
Show me.
You think I'm that weak?
I'd live a thousand years
with this on my shoulders
before I pull this trigger.
You will... eventually.
One bullet for one man.
No!
What... what...
what are you doing?
I found my way out.
You killed Vance.
- you killed Perry...
- Fuck.
But you're still alive. Dan.
That doesn't mean anything!
Ah. let's see.
- Argh...!
- Mm! Please.
No. no! Please stop!
Please don't hurt him.
Fuck.
Come on.
Alright. brother. come on.
No.
Fucking...
burn this house down.
Burn his fucking memories.
Burn his fucking
fucked-up family.
Ah!
...all fucking locked up.
I let you go.
Uh. yeah.
guess that was a mistake.
This is what you wanted.
isn't it?
It was.
Now I just wanna see you burn.
Argh!! Fuck!
Fuck!
Bitch.
Huh? C'mere.
C'mere. C'mon.
Ah!!
Ah!!! Ah!
I've got an idea.
Ah! Ah!
Ah! No!
Don't!
No!
Don't! Ah!
Ah!!
One last walk
down memory lane.
Hold still! I'll give it to you
like Daddy did. just like Papa.
Be a good little girl.
It'll be over soon.
Hold still. Daddy's little girl.
Little angel.
Yeah. that's it. just lie there.
you broken little bitch.
Hey! Stop!
Ah! Stop. stop. stop. stop!
Stop! Stop!
This won't bring Vance back!
No more killing.
I forgive you.
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
WEB-DL resync by GoldenBeard
www.addic7ed.com
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today